howdini.com 2019-03-17

# Howdini.com - Privacy Policy

**LAST UPDATED: MAY 24, 2018**

Howdini is owned by Touchstorm, LLC, a division of Diginary Holdings, with offices at 9011 Arboretum Parkway, Suite 210, Richmond, VA 23236 (“Touchstorm”). Touchstorm is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes the information that we collect from you through the www.Howdini.com website (the “Site”), the purposes for which we use such information, with whom we may share such information, your choices regarding our use and sharing of such information, and the steps we take to protect your personal information. By accessing the Site, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site. Except as provided in the “Your California Privacy Rights” section below, this Privacy Policy only applies to information collected on the Site and does not apply to information which we may collect on other websites owned or operated by Touchstorm or by means other than on the Site. 

**Topics:**  
**1. _Your California Privacy Rights_  
2. ** ** _Information We Collect About You_**  
    2.1 Information Collected Directly From You  
    2.2 Information Collected Automatically  
    2.3 Our Use of Cookies; Third Party Cookies; Web Beacons  
    2.4 Aggregate Information  
**3. _How We Use The Information About You_**  
    3.1 Disclosure of Your Personal Information  
    3.2 Disclosure Regarding Service Providers  
    3.3 Disclosures In Connection With Acquisitions Or Divestitures  
    3.4 Disclosure For Other Reasons  
**4. __** ** _Marketing_**  
**5. __** ** _Security_**  
    5.1 Information Storage and Security  
    5.2 How Long We Keep Information  
          5.2.1 Marketing Information  
**6. __** ** _Access To Your Information And Correction_**  
**7. __** ** _Other Websites_**  
**8. __** ** _Additional Information_**  
    8.1 Note to International Users  
    8.2 Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance  
    8.3 Enforcement Of This Privacy Statement  
    8.4 Changes To This Privacy Statement  
**9. __** ** _How To Contact Us_**

* * *

**_1\. Your California Privacy Rights_  
**The following only applies to California residents who have an established business relationship with Diginary Software. If we collect your name or other personal information from you (whether online or offline), and you have given us permission to share your personal information by clicking on the appropriate box or button on the Site or by any other means we may provide, we may occasionally make that personal information available to our parent or other affiliated companies, or to other third parties (including, but not limited to, our clients) who have products or services that we believe will be of interest to you, for their direct marketing purposes. If you later decide that you do not want us to share your personal information with these companies for their direct marketing purposes, please contact us at [**_privacypolicy@howdini.com_**](mailto:privacypolicy@howdini.com). Your opt out request will be processed within ten (10) business days of the date on which we receive it. For more information on how your personal information is collected, used and shared, please read the remainder of this Privacy Policy. 

**_2\. Information We Collect About You_  
**We collect information about you in the following ways:

**2.1 Information Collected Directly From You  
**You can visit the Site and access the information available on the Site without entering any personal information. However, when you sign up for an account in order to access certain information, services, or features that may be contained on the Site, we may require you to provide personal information such as your name, email address, phone number, occupation, company information, video titles, YouTube links, keywords, categories, and other data. For example, we will collect certain personal information if you choose to register on the Site, join our email list, subscribe to our newsletter or blog, participate in special offers, sweepstakes, contests or other promotions, sign up for our chat rooms, message boards or other public venues or send questions or comments to us via email.

**2.2 Information Collected Automatically  
**We may collect information about your visit to the Site, including what pages you view, the number of bytes transferred, the links you click, the materials you access, and other actions taken within the Site. We may also collect certain standard information that your browser sends to every website you visit, such as your Internet Protocol address, your browser type and capabilities and language, your operating system, the date and time you access the Site, and the website from which you linked to our Site. We do not link this information to your personal information.

**2.3 Our Use of Cookies; Third Party Cookies; Web Beacons  
**Cookies are small files that websites save to your hard disk or to your browser’s memory. We may use them to track the number of times you have visited the Site, to track the number of visitors to the Site, to determine and analyze visitors use of the Site (including the effectiveness of online advertising), to store information that you provide such as your preferences, and to store technical information useful for your interactions with the Site. We may use session cookies (cookies that are deleted when your browser session ends) to facilitate your movement around the Site (particularly in connection with information searches) and to store other information useful in administering the session. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser settings to decline cookies or to notify you when a cookie is being placed on your computer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the features of the Site. Refer to your specific browser’s Help menu for details. You may occasionally get cookies from our advertisers or other third parties with links on the Site. We do not control these cookies. The use of advertising cookies sent by third-party servers is standard in the Internet industry. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personal information you submit while on the Site. Our Site may also contain electronic images known as web beacons sometimes called single-pixel gifs that allow us to count the number of users who have beacons in promotional email messages or newsletters in order to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon.

**2.4 Aggregate Information  
**From time to time, we may collect general, non-personal, statistical information about the use of the Site, such as how many visitors visit a specific page on the Site, how long they stay on that page, and which hyperlinks, if any, they “click” on. For details about how we collect this information, see “Information Collected Automatically” section above. We collect this information in order to determine which areas of the Site are most popular and to enhance the Site for visitors. We may also group this information into aggregate visitor data in order to describe the use of the Site to our existing or potential business partners, clients or other third parties, or in response to a government request. However, please be assured that this aggregate data will in no way personally identify you or any other visitors to the Site.

**_3\. How We Use The Information About You_**

**3.1 Disclosure of Your Personal Information  
**Except as described in this document, personal information you provide to Touchstorm through the Site will not be shared outside of Diginary Holdings and its service providers without your permission.

If you provide us with personal information, we may retain and use that information for several purposes. For example, we may use your personal information in order to provide information and services that you request such as responding to questions and sending emails to our email list subscribers. In addition, we may use your personal information to ensure compliance with Touchstorm’s policies and applicable law. In order to offer you a more consistent experience in your interactions with the Site, information collected via the Site may be combined with information we collect by other means. We may also use your personal information to improve the Site, or to make the Site easier to use by eliminating the need for you to repeatedly enter the same information or by customizing the Site to your particular preference or interests. If you have chosen to receive communications by email from us but later wish to opt out of receiving such communications from us at any time, simply follow the instructions for doing so included in the emails. We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the Site, such as service announcements or similar administrative or transactional messages, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them.

**3.2 Disclosure Regarding Service Providers  
**Touchstorm contracts with other companies to provide services on our behalf, such as hosting websites, sending out information, and analyzing the Site. We provide these companies with only those elements of your personal information they need to deliver those services. These companies and their employees are prohibited from using that personal information for any other purpose.

**3.3 Disclosures In Connection With Acquisitions Or Divestitures  
**Circumstances may arise where for strategic or other business reasons Touchstorm decides to sell, buy, merge or otherwise reorganize its own or other businesses. Such a transaction may involve the disclosure of personal and other information to prospective or actual purchasers, or receiving it from sellers. It is Touchstorm’s practice to seek appropriate protection for information in these types of transactions. In the event that Touchstorm or all of its assets are acquired in such a transaction, customer information would be one of the transferred assets.

**3.4 Disclosure For Other Reasons  
**We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with legal requirements or with legal process served on us, to protect and defend our rights or property, or in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of any individual.

**_4\. Marketing_  
**We would like to send you information about products and services of ours and other companies in our group which may be of interest to you. If you have consented to receive marketing, you may opt out at a later date.

You have a right at any time to stop us from contacting you for marketing purposes or giving your information to other companies within Diginary Holdings. We will not share your information for marketing purposes with companies outside of Diginary Holdings.

If you no longer wish to be contacted for marketing purposes, please contact us at [**_privacypolicy@howdini.com_**](mailto:privacypolicy@howdini.com). Your opt out request(s) will be processed within ten (10) business days of the date on which we receive it.

**_5\. Security_**

**5.1 Information Storage and Security  
**Touchstorm is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, use data hosting service providers in the United States to host the information we collect, and we use technical measures to secure your data. While we implement safeguards designed to protect your information, no security system is impenetrable and due to the inherent nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee that data, during transmission through the Internet or while stored on our systems or otherwise in our care, is absolutely safe from intrusion by others. 

If you register for an account on the Site, you will be asked to choose a password for your account, in which case, your online account information shall be protected by your password. We recommend that you do not disclose your password to any other person. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password and account, and are fully responsible for all activities that occur under your password or account.

**5.2 How Long We Keep Information  
**How long we keep information we collect about you depends on the type of information, as described in further detail below. After such time, we will either delete or anonymize your information or, if this is not possible (for example, because the information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your information and isolate it from any further use until deletion is possible.

**5.2.2 Marketing Information:** If you have elected to receive marketing emails from us, we retain information about your marketing preferences unless you specifically ask us to delete such information. We retain information derived from cookies and other tracking technologies for a reasonable period of time from the date such information was created. 

**_6\. Access To Your Information And Correction_  
**You have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. We want to make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. You may ask us to correct or remove information you think is inaccurate. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please contact us at [**_privacypolicy@howdini.com_**](mailto:privacypolicy@howdini.com). Your information and/or correction request(s) will be processed within ten (10) business days of the date on which we receive it and will be provided in a common machine-readable format, for example as a .csv file.

**_7\. Other Websites_  
**Our website contains links to other websites. This Privacy Policy only applies to this website so when you link to other websites you should read their own Privacy Policies.

**_8\. Additional Information_**

**8.1 A Note To International Users  
**The Site is hosted in the United States. If you are accessing the Site from outside the United States, by providing your information to the Site, you are consenting to the transfer of your information to the United States for processing and maintenance in accordance with this Privacy Policy and our [**_Terms and Conditions_**](https://www.howdini.com/terms-and-conditions). You are also consenting to the application of United States law in all matters concerning the Site. Diginary Holdings makes makes it a practice to be aware of and comply, to the best of our ability, with International privacy best practices and laws, however, Diginary Holdings makes no representation that this Privacy Policy and such practices comply with the laws of every other country.

**8.2 Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance  
**Our website, products, and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. In compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not knowingly collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age.

**8.3 Enforcement Of This Privacy Policy  
**If you have questions regarding this Privacy Policy or our handling of your personal information, please contact us at [**_privacypolicy@howdini.com_**](mailto:privacypolicy@howdini.com). Your email will receive a response within ten (10) business days of the date on which we receive it.

**8.4 Changes To This Privacy Policy  
**We may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we do, we will post a notice on the homepage of the Site for a reasonable period of time after such changes are made that this Privacy Policy has been updated, and we will revise the “Last Updated” date at the top of this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to check this page periodically for any updates. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of updates to this Privacy Policy will mean you accept those updates.

**_9\. How To Contact Us_  
**Please contact us if you have any questions about our Privacy Policy or information we hold about you:

  * By email to Diana Papaleo, Diginary Holdings’ Data Protection Officer, directly at [**_DPO@diginaryholdings.com_**](mailto:DPO@diginaryholdings.com). Your email will receive a response within ten (10) business days of the date on which we receive it.
  * Or write to us at: Diginary Holdings, ATTN: Diana Papaleo / DPO, 9011 Arboretum Parkway, Suite 210, Richmond, VA 23236, United States of America. A response to your mailed communication will be sent within ten (10) business days of the date on which we receive it.
